(Howard:)Hey, Bernie.
Hey. How's my little astronauttie hottie?
(Howard:)Okay, I guess.
(Howard:)It's just being cooped up in this tin can
for weeks on end is starting to get to me.
(Bernadette:)Hang in there. You just have a couple
more days to go and you'll be home.
- I know.
- I gotta get back to work. I love you.
(Howard:)Love you too. Hey, Bernie...
(Howard:)...before you go,
can you do something for me?
(Bernadette:)What do you want me to do?
(Howard:)Okay, here it is.
(Howard:)I really miss gravity.
(Howard:)Can you drop something
so I can watch it fall?
Really? You're serious?
(Howard:)Okay.
(Howard:)Oh, baby, you're killing me.
Unh. Hey, Sheldon? Hi.
(Penny:)This came for you today.
It's from your mom.